{
  "answers": [
    {
      "question": "1",
      "answer": "Russia"
    },
    {
      "question": "2",
      "answer": "1914"
    },
    {
      "question": "3",
      "answer": "Great white shark"
    },
    {
      "question": "4",
      "answer": "Blue"
    },
    {
      "question": "5",
      "answer": "India"
    },
    {
      "question": "6",
      "answer": "Cheetah"
    },
    {
      "question": "7",
      "answer": "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs"
    },
    {
      "question": "8",
      "answer": "Jakarta"
    },
    {
      "question": "9",
      "answer": "1984"
    },
    {
      "question": "10",
      "answer": "Replicants"
    }
  ]
}
